Guide to the Rioghan Kirchner Civil Rights in Brooklyn Collection BCMS.0011
Brooklyn Collection
- Series IV: Black News
  - Volume 4
    - No. 16, 1981 January (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Christmas On The Plantation
      The East Visits Clinton Prison
      Atlanta's Missing and Murdered Black Children
    - No. 17, 1981 April (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Defend Or Die
      East Organization Members Held Hostage in Israel
      Government-Klan Complicity In The Greenboro Killings
      Community Responds To Mardi Gras Shooting
      Support Shown For Our Children In Atlanta
      Save Our Children
      Colonial Violence and Terror Stalks Atlanta and U.S.
      The Black Holocaust and The Genocide Convention In The 80's
      Cases Of Police Brutality
      Congolese National Liberation Front
      Open Letter To The Black Hostage Charles Jones
      Food Science
      Larry Neal...Black Arts Figure Dies
      Grenada
    - No. 18, 1981 August (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Editorial Briefs
      Marley Remembered
      BUF Attends Conference On South Africa
      The Betrayal Of The Black Nation
      On Being Black In Black Afrika
      Granada Responds To CBS
      East Members Visit Cuba
      Bob Marley Comes To Harlem
      How Diet Can Effect Your Behavior
      Going Home
      Black Women Respond To Atlanta
      Natural Movement
      In Memoriam Of A Fallen Soldier – Irving Davis
    - No. 19, 1981 October (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Vann Halts City Elections
      National Black United Front Solidarity Tour '81
      What Killed Sadat Treachery or Terrorism?
      Carifta Cottages 21 and 22
      International Organ Supports S.A. Women
      The British Dilemma: From Rebellion To Royalty
      Britain: A Community Under Attack
      Grenada...Small Nation – Big Revolution
      Dessie Woods Is Free!
      Fairfield Towers Tenant Assoc.
      Kalamu Yasalaam Receives Music Awards
      The Voting Rights Act
      Ahidiana's 4th Annual Black Womens Conference
    - No. 20, 1982 February (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Manley's PNP Blasts Seaga's Anti-Cuban Move
      Spouse Abuse: A Black On Black Crime
      Ella McQueen
      Who Are The Retail Terrorists?
      Ministry Of National Mobilization! A People's Ministry
      Pan-Afrikan Science Skills Chap.8
      The Rapid Deployment Force, The Ugly American Is The World's Policeman
      POW Forum T.B. Epidemic
      Sugar Madness
      The Incarceration Of Japanese Americans During World War 2
      Scarman - What He won't Say
      BUF Holds Forum On Law Enforcement
      Malcolm X – His Significance and Legacy
      Miriam Makeba
    - No. 21, 1982 May (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Upcoming Events
      Malcolm and The Messenger
      To Have A Dream. Medgar Evers College
      Black Legislators – Call For Resolution To Evers Crisis
      Bishop Calls For New World Information Order
      Energy and Power
      Bay Area Blacks and The Movement Towards A Strategic National Black Consensus In The USA
      Black and Nuclear Disarmament
      A Third World Perspective On Nuclear Disarmament
      Al Vann Seeks Reelection
      Causes Of High Blood Pressure Among Blacks
      POW Forum – Breakout Attempt At Marion Penitentiary
      White Racist Stabbed on 2nd Day at Marion Penitentiary
      Tennessee Murder In The 1st Degree
      Night Flight To Bagdad
      The Joy and Pain Of Single Parenting
      Black Folks Guide To Making Big Money In America
    - No. 22, 1982 August (Box 10, Folder 3)
      The Socio-Political Philosophy Of Marcus Garvey
      Political Journalist and The Black Liberation Movement
      Shaka Zulu: The Spirit Lives On
      The Iceman Inheritance (book report)
      Black Community Response To Israel's Genocidal War Against Palestinian People
      The Black Family: A Troubled Institution?
      Black Community Uproar At Schomburg
      POW's Forum-Necessity Of Armed Freedom Fighters
      Heroes and Martyrs Of The 20th Century
      International Tribunal On Reparations for Black People In The U.S.
      Tribute To Jacques Stephen Alexis
      Where The Lawless Are The Law
      Pres. Samora Machel Of Mozambique visits Grenada
      Open Letter To The Brothers Johnson
      Justice is Just-us
      Report On African Liberation Day – In England
      Human Rights Conference Planned For N.Y.
      Time On The Cross!!!
      A Surprising Path To Black Unity
    - No. 23, 1982 November (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Calendar Of Events
      Blacks Collaborate With State To Destroy Uhuru Sasa
      Beyond Blurred Vision In The Middle East
      Being A Black Child In New York
      Check It Out – "A Soldiers Play"
      Interview With Dr. M.R. Karenga Creator Of Kwanza
      Blacks Under Siege
      Black and Hispanic Vote Elects Cuomo
      Sisters Unite
      Thanksgiving and Black Family Unity Day
      Steel Pulse Comes To Uhuru Center
      Zaire Oppression
      Shaka Memorial
      Where Are The Warriors? The Case Of Mumia Abu Jamal
      Brooklyn Youth Visit Grenada
      Herpes...Death To The Sexual Revolution
      Mayor Carihan Not Guilty
    - No. 24, 1983 May (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Up Coming Events
      Umoja House- Turning Gangs Into Guardians
      Four Accused in Bomb Trial Sentenced To Hang
      A Haven Away From Haiti
      Ending Cultural Collaboration Striking A Blow For Afrikan Liberation
      Checking It Out "Tony Brown's Journal"
      X-rays – Get The Picture On Protection
    - No. 25, 1983 August (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Interview with historian activist Dr. John Henrik Clarke
      Running a Black Presidential Candidate: Pros, cons and caveats
      Sun Ra Upsets Kool Festival
      Book Review: Introduction to Black Studies
      Nutrition
      Herschel the Gladiator
      Libya's Gathafi [Muammar Gaddafi] Speaks Out on Racism
      The Nation of Islam is in the Fish Business
      Mississippi Tenants Fight for Survival
      Heroes and Martyrs of the 20th Century
  - Volume 5
    - No. 1, 1983 December (Box 10, Folder 5)
      The Case Of Michael Stewart
      The 3rd Trial For Labord and York
      City Awards $150,000 In Chase Death
      Notes On Saviors' Day 1983
      Shadowbrook Tenants Victorious
      Grenada: Truth Crushed To The Earth
      An Old Tune
      Cuba Speaks
      World Assembly For Peace
      Making Of A Racist Health Therapist
      First In Neo-Slavery
      Sunny Ade's Juju Music
      Book Review – At War
      Partisan Labels
    - No. 2, 1984 February (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Grenada: Black Medical Student Speaks
      Jesse Jackson's Mission To Syria
      Nicky Barnes Sings The Blues
      APSP Offer Prisoner Exchange For Goodman
      Melba Liston
      At War On The Black Child
      Capital Punishment
      Black Veteran Visits Nicaragua
      Ghana Today
      Book Review "House Of Slammers"
      Checking It Out "Pieces Of A Dream"